Jesus Salcedo

Software Developer



I'm a fullstack web developer with great interest in Javascript technologies like Angular, Vue and React, graphic designer also passionate about art and video games. I love backend development with Node, Python and C# and SQL Databases.

I like to constantly explore and research technology and new practices, exchange knowledge in developer communities, learn more and do what I love giving my best in every project and work team. Always open to new ideas and assume the challenges that arise with the best disposition and learn from them.

Experience

Catasig (Nov 2022 - Jun 2023)

Full stack Developer

Fullstack Development and maintenance of a government applications for the land registry manager in the Colombian Catastro.

- Frontend and backend development for the Avaluo catastral Web application using Nextjs, React, Nodejs and Postgres SQL Databases.
- UI design and frontend development of Catasig website using Angular and Docker & Nginx for deployment.
- Frontend development and UI design for Catasig Geoserver using Vuels, Mapbox API for the map inplementation and Backend development using Django and Docker with Postgres Databases.

Orusxpert SAS (Jan 2022 - Oct 2022)

Full stack Developer

Software development for the generation, edition and calculation of routes, with the purpose of simplifying and improving the routing process for the location of clients and commercial representatives in each area, for the company Ab-Inbev. Functions performed:

- Frontend implementation based on mockups provided under the Figma tool for the interfaces using Angular as the main base of the project and integrating additional tools such as Google API, Material UI and PrimeNG for the interfaces.
- Backend development through the creation of Microservices using Python (Django) and Postgresql for the connection to the database.
- Software maintenance and deployment in Google Cloud, using Docker.

Mr Cake Store (Jun 2020 - Aug 2020)

Full stack Developer

Development of an ecommerce website for a small company dedicated to the sale of confectionery. Using PHP (Codeigniter) for the backend development and Javascript (Bootstrap, Ajax, Datatables and jQuery) for the frontend.

DATASCOM SAS (Sept 2017 - Dec 2019)

Full stack Developer Junior

Linked to a small software company dedicated to the development of solutions for medical equipment and pharmacies.

Functions performed:

- Design of icons and multimedia material for risk management app with Adobe Illustrator design
- UI design for SIE medical equipment management project.
- Frontend implementation for a pharmacy management project and SIE medical equipment management project, with HTML5, CSS3, Javascript (Ajax and jQuery) technologies.
- Development of backend for the pharmacy administration system. Using C# .NET with Devexpress and Postgresql for database connection.

Projects and Contributions

liquidapp

#react #nextjs #prisma #redux #HTML5 #node #tailwindcss

Application for catastral manager and appraisal settlement developed in React and node using Next as the main framework, prisma and Postgres.

passcracker

#python #shell

Password cracker in typical hashing methods with password generator.

note-calculator

#material #HTML5 #jquery

Development of a simple Javascript application for the calculation of the remaining score in the useful very

to know how much you need to win the period.

ink-portfolio

#react #HTML5 #purecss #gatsby #graphql

Design and development of a tattoo artist and illustrator portfolio, where my illustrations and artistic projects are exhibited as a product of my career as a graphic designer.

movie-dashboard

#react #SASS #nodejs #tailwindcss

Development of an application in react for the connection to movie API, it can be used as a base project for dashboards.

Skills

Frontend

React, Angular, jQuery, Axios, HTML5, CSS, SASS, Material, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS and NextJs.

Languages

English B2 **Spanish** Native

Backend

NodeJs, Python, C#, SQL Databases, Firebase and Mongodb.

Others

Adobe Xd, Figma, Photoshop, SCRUM, Git and Iira

Education

Software Development

Corporación Universitaria Empresarial de Salamanca CUES (2013 - 2016)

Graphic and multimedia production Institución Universitaria ITSA (2018 - 2020)